[
    {
        "Question": "elaborately",
        "Answer": "with great detail",
        "Options": "well develop/ development"
    },
    {
        "Question": "astoundingly",
        "Answer": "incredibly",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "cramped",
        "Answer": "confined",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "impediment",
        "Answer": "obstruction",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "so much for",
        "Answer": "that is enough about",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "segregated",
        "Answer": "separated",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "installed",
        "Answer": "put in place",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "shortcoming",
        "Answer": "weakness",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "contradictory",
        "Answer": "conflicting",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "persisted",
        "Answer": "continued",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "sloping",
        "Answer": "inclining",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "pierced",
        "Answer": "broke through",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "obsolete",
        "Answer": "out of date",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "hence",
        "Answer": "therefore",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "available",
        "Answer": "obtainable",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "deficiencies",
        "Answer": "shortages",
        "Options": "inadequate"
    },
    {
        "Question": "vanishes",
        "Answer": "disappears",
        "Options": "enormous/ huge"
    },
    {
        "Question": "miniature",
        "Answer": "small",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "propulsion",
        "Answer": "moving forward",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "posed",
        "Answer": "presented",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "efficacy",
        "Answer": "effectiveness",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "prevail",
        "Answer": "dominate",
        "Options": "most frequent"
    },
    {
        "Question": "sponsored",
        "Answer": "supported",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "accumulated",
        "Answer": "collected",
        "Options": "gather"
    },
    {
        "Question": "converted",
        "Answer": "changed",
        "Options": "transform"
    },
    {
        "Question": "cumbersome",
        "Answer": "burdensome",
        "Options": "clumsy"
    },
    {
        "Question": "advance",
        "Answer": "improvement",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "clues",
        "Answer": "information",
        "Options": "hints"
    },
    {
        "Question": "circumstances",
        "Answer": "conditions",
        "Options": "situation"
    },
    {
        "Question": "eradicate",
        "Answer": "remove completely",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "notion",
        "Answer": "idea",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "robust",
        "Answer": "healthy",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "projected",
        "Answer": "shown",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "brittle",
        "Answer": "breakable",
        "Options": "fragile"
    },
    {
        "Question": "lamented",
        "Answer": "complained about",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "exceed",
        "Answer": "go beyond",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "dramatically",
        "Answer": "greatly",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "constrain",
        "Answer": "restrict",
        "Options": "limit"
    },
    {
        "Question": "obscure",
        "Answer": "little known",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "equilibrium",
        "Answer": "balance",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "agencies",
        "Answer": "forces",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "administer",
        "Answer": "manage",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "ephemeral",
        "Answer": "short-lived",
        "Options": "transient"
    },
    {
        "Question": "covered",
        "Answer": "included",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "intensive",
        "Answer": "strong",
        "Options": "extreme"
    },
    {
        "Question": "disturb",
        "Answer": "upset",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "comes close",
        "Answer": "approaches",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "yet",
        "Answer": "however",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "refined",
        "Answer": "improved",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "reveal",
        "Answer": "show",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "indigenous",
        "Answer": "native",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "discharge",
        "Answer": "release",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "albeit",
        "Answer": "though",
        "Options": "even though"
    },
    {
        "Question": "elaborate",
        "Answer": "detailed",
        "Options": "complex"
    },
    {
        "Question": "invoked",
        "Answer": "called upon",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "incentives",
        "Answer": "motivation",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "excavated",
        "Answer": "dug from the groud",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "restricted",
        "Answer": "limited",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "particular",
        "Answer": "specific",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "peak",
        "Answer": "high point",
        "Options": "maximum"
    },
    {
        "Question": "relatively",
        "Answer": "comparatively",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "assimilated",
        "Answer": "absorbed",
        "Options": "combined"
    },
    {
        "Question": "remarkable",
        "Answer": "extraordinary",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "commonly",
        "Answer": "often",
        "Options": "generally/ normally"
    },
    {
        "Question": "subdue",
        "Answer": "defeat",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "novel",
        "Answer": "innovative",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "essential",
        "Answer": "fundamental",
        "Options": "integral"
    },
    {
        "Question": "amazing",
        "Answer": "remarkable",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "paradoxes",
        "Answer": "contradictions",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "ancient",
        "Answer": "antique",
        "Options": "old"
    },
    {
        "Question": "component",
        "Answer": "part/ constituent",
        "Options": "element"
    },
    {
        "Question": "dictate",
        "Answer": "determine",
        "Options": "order"
    },
    {
        "Question": "aggregate",
        "Answer": "combined/ group",
        "Options": "overall"
    },
    {
        "Question": "plugged",
        "Answer": "filled up",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "approach",
        "Answer": "come nearer to/ move toward",
        "Options": "method"
    },
    {
        "Question": "constituent",
        "Answer": "component",
        "Options": "comprise"
    },
    {
        "Question": "perplexed",
        "Answer": "puzzled",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "embark on",
        "Answer": "start",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "vast",
        "Answer": "extensive",
        "Options": "largely"
    },
    {
        "Question": "exclusively",
        "Answer": "solely",
        "Options": "only"
    },
    {
        "Question": "provided",
        "Answer": "if",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "perishable",
        "Answer": "likely to decay",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "arduous",
        "Answer": "difficult",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "drive",
        "Answer": "incentive",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "configurations",
        "Answer": "arrangements",
        "Options": "shape/ forms"
    },
    {
        "Question": "drawn to",
        "Answer": "attracted toward",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "stationary",
        "Answer": "unmoving/ nonmoving",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "deposit",
        "Answer": "accumulate",
        "Options": "lay down"
    },
    {
        "Question": "establishment",
        "Answer": "formation",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "outlining",
        "Answer": "summarizing",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "fringes",
        "Answer": "borders",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "consist of",
        "Answer": "compose of",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "archive",
        "Answer": "record",
        "Options": "store"
    },
    {
        "Question": "merge",
        "Answer": "combine",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "pales",
        "Answer": "loses significance",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "dual",
        "Answer": "double",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "inadvertently",
        "Answer": "unintentionally",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "therefore",
        "Answer": "as a result",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "compensates for",
        "Answer": "makes up for",
        "Options": "reimburse"
    },
    {
        "Question": "thus",
        "Answer": "consequently",
        "Options": ""
    }
]